Hello hello everyone welcome to my YouTube
channel our topic today is
about ICICI Lombard's Help Plus product
that ICC Lombard has upgraded its product
which is divided into four categories
we are giving you one by one
subscribe to all the products subscribe watch the
video completely first of all we are talking
about help purpose
its first feature is worldwide
treatment
many times such a situation
comes in front of the company that they need treatment outside India
in that case if you have this
policy then you can get your treatment done outside India as well
and the best
thing is that whoever you subscribe to it
midnight will be
zal for example if you have a policy of 50 lakhs if
you have used that 50 lakhs in India
then the company will
subscribe and charge you job appointment
which is a very attractive feature
in this you have to keep in mind that when
you do treatment outside India then
10.00 will be extra that will be given to the policy holder
Now let's talk about the second feature which you are coming to,
when any organ donor organ of the policy holder gets
damaged, then he needs it
and
in such a bad situation the company will also subscribe the policy holder
and the
best thing is that if you do
not subscribe for example no treatment then the cost is not less than ₹3 per month
which is a very great feature now let's talk
about its features which you have a
super no claim bonus on
super no claim bonus, whenever
any of your money is free then you can
subscribe to it which is now subscribed on the skin, for
example if someone has a policy of 20 lakh
rupees if he does not subscribe then
those more subscriptions have
very attractive features because the
perception is much higher after the super no
claim bonus,
now let's talk about its fourth feature
which is your additional commission bonus, you should
not be confused in this, in this the company can subscribe in two ways,
subscribe my channel you will
not have to subscribe if you are a designated
subscriber
now let's talk  Their next feature
is your Ad Protector, it means if you
appoint an Additional Director then
you get No Claim Bonus and Super Appointment,
click on Withdrawal and if the amount is
below Rs. 50,000 then this payment of
No Claim Bonus of Additional Secretary is complete,
this NAAC feature of this is Maternity
Benefit, if you have taken this policy then you
can apply for this coverage
and the maximum coverage will be Rs.
50,000 in Caesarean delivery and up
to Rs. 25 in normal delivery, the maximum
limit of NAAC is Rs. 1 lakh.
Now let's talk about NAAC Twitter, which is
your Unlimited Recent Benefit,
as soon as the policy holder comments time is
over, the company subscribes me to the
contract appointment, this was earlier available only once in a year,
now it can be
available multiple times, attractive features
like
air ambulance, you can use it up-to-the-minute the
next day, the same thing is that the
deduction you will get will not be less than your time
That too will be additional Apart from this, other
subscriptions Subscribe Ayurvedic
treatment Subscribe Mistreatment of
Subscribe Ambulance cover Television station
available Velvet Subscribe Online chat
Doctor opinion Subscribe for hospital
Birthday is available Sui is a past lot of
information about the product
Apart from this, our personal suggestion is that this is a
very competitive product in the market
Isi Lumba has launched information
about Meghnad Plus Cover information about these products
in videos Please
like our channel and subscribe Thank
you
What happened